

Arkadiusz Nowak

Email: arkadiusz.nowak.2022@gmail.com

Phone: +31 622527412

Date of birth: 04-06-1989

Town: Dordrecht

Portfolio: https://arkadiusznowak.netlify.app

Profile

Knowledge of JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Sass, jQuery, Bootstrap, React, Redux Toolkit, TypeScript.

Experience in C++ programming.

Experience in Java programming.

Experience in RAPID programming.

Creating welding processes in laser beam technology, TIG and MIG-MAG method.

Manipulating ABB and Kawasaki robots.

Developing technology of welding.

Supervision of technology and equipment for welding stations.

Personnel management.

Project management.

Work experience

07.2019 - 12.2021 [2 y. 6 m.]

KONI B.V., Netherlands Welding Robot Specialist

Welding components with automatic MIG-MAG welding processes. Manipulating ABB robots in automatic and manual mode. Programming robots, writing and understanding RAPID language. Understanding robot's reactions for software. Validating robot's positions, creating welding processes and manipulating the current ones, creating new steps for robots related to servo mechanisms. Reading technical drawings.

Knowing welding processes, effects and behaviours according to experience in the welding sector and new documentations.

Additionally programming 2-Axis CNC Lathe Machine; reading drawings, taking measurements, creating programs for outside turning in Style Control 2015 Edition software.

AIC S.A., Poland

Leading Specialist In Manufacturing Processes Department

Project management. Personnel management. Supplying department with new tools and materials. Controlling the validation of new production systems supported by automatic laser beam welding and automatic TIG methods. I was supervising the work of our technicians, collaborating with robotics engineers and other specialists. I was creating welding processes in new projects. My job also involved monitoring current automatic welding processes and being responsible for production flow in the automatic area.

12.2016 - 03.2018 [1 y. 4 m.]

AIC S.A., Poland

Welding Processes Specialist In Technology Department

Creating and validating welding processes on new workplaces, which were constructed for welding in laser beam technology and TIG method. I was planning these workplaces and collaborating with robotics engineers who were my support. I was responsible for creating new welding processes in welding machines, making tests and validations, writing workplace manuals, and training new production operators. Mechanical and electrical works. Creating applications with C++, which operators were using for reporting their quantities, problems etc. Creating algorithms in C++ responsible for managing collected data and transforming this data into different reports.

10.2014 - 11.2016 [2 y. 2 m.]

AIC S.A., Poland

Laser Welding Machine Operator

Operator responsible for welding in laser beam technology which was supported by Kawasaki and ABB robots. I was preparing heat exchanger's elements by welding their parts together with a laser beam in automatic processes.

Education

University of Gdańsk	10.2011 - 05.2014
Bachelor of Geography	
Jonas Schmedtmann's Udemy course	01.2022 - 02.2022
The Complete JavaScript Course 2022	
Akademia108 – Academy of Programming	03.2011 - 06.2014
Front-end developer	

Languages

- English
- Polish

Skills

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- React
- TypeScript
- Microsoft Excel
- RAPID
- Basics of C++ and Java
- LaserNet
- Category B driving licence